- 一颗幽灵星球？  - 我不建议超自然的解释，舰长
- A ghost planet? - I suggest no supernatural explanation, Captain.
但事实并不符合任何已知的行星类别
But the facts do not fit any known categories of planets.
- 让我们看看现实，那应该能解释某些东西  - 毫无疑问
- Let's take the facts. That should explain something. - Undoubtedly.
这个星球的年龄看起来只有几千年
The age of this planet would seem to be only a few thousand years.
植被不可能在这么短的时间内进化
Vegetation cannot evolve in so short a period.
它的大小和地球的月亮差不多
Its size is approximately that of Earth's moon.
但它的质量和大气与地球相似
But its mass and its atmosphere are similar to Earth.
- 这很难解释  - 这不可能，舰长
- That would be difficult to explain. - It would be impossible, Captain.
大气不可能演变得这么快
An atmosphere could not evolve so quickly.
- 然而它就是如此  - 显然
- And yet it has. - Evidently.
但这种不一致呈现出一种看似不可能的现象
But the inconsistencies present a seemingly impossible phenomenon.
- 但是很迷人，史波克先生  - 没错，舰长
- But a fascinating one, Mr. Spock. - Precisely, Captain.
如果我们要给星际舰队提供一份准确的报告，则需要进一步调查
It would bear closer investigation if we are to provide Starfleet with an accurate report.
上尉，让麦考伊医生到传送室加入调查小队
Lieutenant, send Dr. McCoy to the transporter room for survey party.
我们还需要高级地质学家达马托
We'll also need Senior Geologist D'Amato.
把传送坐标发给传送室，苏鲁先生，你跟我走
Feed beam down coordinates to the transporter room. Mr. Sulu, you'll accompany me.
史波克先生，你来掌舵
Mr. Spock, you have the conn.
拉达上尉，立即到舰桥报告
Lieutenant Radha, report to the bridge immediately.
这次探险应该是地质学家的梦想
This expedition should be a geologist's dream.
有机会探索如此年轻的星球是幸运的
The opportunity to explore so young a planet is lucky.
是的，如果史波克先生是对的，你会有一份震惊星际地球物理会议的报告
Yes. If Mr. Spock is correct, you'll have a report to startle the Interstellar Geophysical Conference.
- 为什么？它是什么，吉姆？  - 一个连史波克都无法解释的行星
- Why? What is it, Jim? - A planet even Spock can't explain.
准备传送
Prepare to transport.
启动
Energize.
等等！你们不能去
Wait! You must not go.
吉姆，你看到我看到的了吗？
Jim, did you see what I saw?
那个女人袭击了怀亚特少尉，柯克呼叫…
That woman attacked Ensign Wyatt. Kirk to...
舰长！
Captain!
[爆炸]
[EXPLOSION]
史波克先生，你还好吗？
Mr. Spock, are you all right?
是的，我认为没有造成永久性伤害
Yes. I believe no permanent damage was done.
发生了什么？
What happened?
我的后脑勺好像撞到了椅子的扶手
The occipital area of my head seems to have impacted with the arm of the chair.
不，史波克先生，我是说我们发生了什么事？
No, Mr. Spock. I meant what happened to us?
这个我们还没有查明
That we have yet to ascertain.
史波克先生！星球消失了！
Mr. Spock! The planet's gone!
这个地方有怎样的地震？
What kind of earthquakes do they have in this place?
我不知道，再这样震法也许能撕裂这个星球
I don't know. Any more like that would tear this planet apart.
舰长，我们感受到的地震，如果刚刚是的话…
Captain, this tremor we felt, if that's what it was...
它完全不像我以前感觉到的地震扰动
and it's certainly like no seismic disturbance I've felt before.
我读到了几乎不可估量的能量，但它又不在了
I got a reading of almost immeasurable power, but it's not there any more.
地震应力可以解释它吗？
Could seismic stress account for it?
我得到的读数与地震力无关
The reading I got had nothing to do with a seismic force.
很奇怪，还有那个女人，柯克呼叫企业号
That's very strange. And that woman. Kirk to Enterprise.
企业号，请回答
Enterprise, come in.
震动可能把它弄坏了
The shock may have damaged it.
它消失了！
It's gone!
企业号，消失了！
The Enterprise. It's gone!
他是对的，那里什么都没有
He's right. There's nothing there.
它怎么会消失？吉姆，那到底是什么意思？
How could it be gone? What the devil does that mean, Jim?
一方面…这意味着我们被困了
For one thing... it means we're stranded.
[柯克] 宇宙，最后的边疆
[Kirk] Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
幸存之物
That Which Survives
企业号一定是爆炸了
The Enterprise must have blown up.
那能解释高辐射读数，不是吗，舰长？如果物质-反物质引擎
That would explain the high-radiation readings, wouldn't it? If the matter-antimatter engines
苏鲁先生，我们不应该停止猜测，并尝试建立一个模式吗
Shouldn't we stop guessing, Mr. Sulu, and try and establish a pattern?
我没有得到高能量强度的读数
I get no readings of high energy concentration.
如果企业号爆炸了，它会留下辐射
If the Enterprise had blown up, it would have left radiation.
会不会是企业号撞击了这个星球？
Could it be the Enterprise hit us, hit the planet?
在西伯利亚曾经有一颗流星巨大到它把森林夷为了平地…
Once in Siberia there was a meteor so great that it flattened forests and was felt as far...
如果我想听俄罗斯历史课，我会带上契科夫
Mr. Sulu, if I'd wanted a Russian history lesson, I'd have brought Chekov.
这是一个生存问题，先生们
This is a matter of survival, gentlemen.
没有企业号，我们需要食物和水，而且我们很快就需要它们
Without the Enterprise, we need food and we need water, and we need them fast.
我要这个星球的详细分析，现在就要
I want a detailed analysis made of this planet and I want it now.
- 是的，长官  - 是的，长官
- Aye, sir. - Yes, sir.
苏鲁先生
Mr. Sulu.
轮机部，无损伤，所有动力水平正常
Engineering, no damage. All power levels normal.
飞船运行正常，有一些磕碰和擦伤
Ship functioning normally. Many bumps and bruises.
一例人员伤亡，传送人员，他死了
One casualty. The transporter officer. He's dead.
死了？
Dead?
史波克呼叫医务室
Spock to Sickbay.
医务室，姆本加医生
Sickbay. Dr. M'Benga.
报告传送人员的死亡情况
Report on the death of the transpoter officer.
我们不确定，桑切斯医生现在正在进行尸检
We're not sure. Dr. Sanchez is conducting an autopsy right now.
嗯…尽快给我一份完整的报告，通话完毕
Mmm... Give me a full report as soon as possible. Spock out.
斯科特先生，检查传送装置是否有故障
Mr. Scott, have the transporter checked for possible malfunction.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
没有任何形式的残骸，我已经进行了两次全面扫描
No debris of any kind. I've made two full scans.
如果这个星球破裂了，会有一些迹象
If the planet had broken up, there would be some sign.
困扰我的是星星，史波克先生
What bothers me is the stars, Mr. Spock.
星星
The stars.
是的，长官，他们不对
Yes, sir. They're wrong.
错误的？
Wrong?
是的，史波克先生
Yes Mr. Spock.
看
Look.
这是爆炸前星星分布的样子
Here's a replay of the star pattern just before the explosion.
位置变化了
A positional change.
这说不通
It doesn't make any sense.
不知为何，在那一瞬间
But somehow I'd say that in a flash
我们被撞到了距我们所在位置1,000光年之外的地方
We've been knocked 1,000 light years away from where we were.
准确地说是990.7光年，上尉
990.7 light years to be exact, Lieutenant.
但这不可能，没有东西能做到
But that's not possible. Nothing can do that.
斯科特先生，既然我们在这里，你的发言既不合逻辑，也不值得反驳
Mr. Scott, since we are here, your statement is not only illogical but also unworthy of refutation.
假设任何爆炸
It is also illogical to assume
即使是一颗恒星变为超新星爆发
that any explosion, even that of a small star going supernova,
把我们扔到990.7光年外，也是不合逻辑的
could have hurled us a distance of 990.7 light years.
它不会把我们扔到什么地方
The point is it shouldn't have hurled us anywhere.
而是会立即摧毁我们，汽化我们
It should have destroyed us immediately, vaporized us!
根据我们知道的定律，没错，斯科特先生
That is correct, Mr. Scott, by all the laws that we know.
没有无意识的时间
There was no period of unconsciousness.
船上的计时器只记录了几秒钟
Our ship's chronometers registered only seconds.
因此，我们被移动了
therefore we were displaced
以某种我无法理解的方式
in some manner which I am unable to fathom.
所以星球没有爆炸
What you're saying is that the planet didn't blow up.
舰长还活着！
And the captain is still alive!
斯科特先生，请克制你不合逻辑的跳跃
Please, Mr. Scott, restrain your leaps of illogic.
我什么都没说，我只是在猜测
I have said nothing. I was merely speculating.
[姆本加] 医务室呼叫史波克先生
[M'Benga] Sickbay to Mr. Spock.
我是史波克
Spock here.
你要求验尸报告
You asked for an autopsy report.
死因似乎是细胞破裂
It's only preliminary, but he cause of death seems to have been cellular disruption.
解释一下
Explain.
仿佛每一个细胞都被从里面炸开
It's as though every cell in the body had been individually blasted from inside.
任何已知的疾病生物会这样做吗？
Would any known disease organism do that?
桑切斯医生已经排除了这一点
Dr. Sanchez has ruled that possibility out, sir.
请随时通知我，通话完毕
Please keep me fully advised. Spock out.
他在传送室
He was in the transporter room.
柯克舰长一行人离开后，可能有人进来了
Someone may have entered after Captain Kirk and his party left.
斯科特先生，由于企业号工作正常
Mr. Scott, since the Enterprise is obviously functional,
我建议让我们以最快的曲速返回我们的起点
I suggest we return to our starting place at top warp speed.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
是的，但我们需要一段时间才能到达那里
But even at that, it will take us a while to get there.
在这种情况下，斯科特先生，我建议我们立即出发
In that case, Mr. Scott, I suggest we start at once.
你能给我曲速8吗？
Can you give me warp 8?
是的，长官，也许更多一点
Aye, sir. And maybe a wee bit more.
我会亲自坐在曲速引擎上照顾它们
I'll sit on the warp engines myself and nurse them.
斯科特先生，那个姿势不仅没有用
That position, Mr. Scott, would not only be unavailing,
还有失体面
but also undignified.
拉达上尉，绘制航线…
Lieutenant Rahda, Plot a course.
已经绘制并设定好了，长官
Already plotted and laid in, sir.
好的，那么准备达到曲速8
Good. Then prepare to come to warp 8.
你的报告涵盖了所有植被？
Your report covers all vegetation?
是的，舰长
Yes, Captain.
所有植物都不能食用，对我们有毒
All vegetation is inedible. Poison to us.
如果企业号被摧毁，你知道我们还能生存多久
If the Enterprise has been destroyed, you know how long we can survive.
是的
Yes.
我没有看到任何水，但一定有才能使植被生长
I don't see any water, but there must be some to grow the vegetation.
水源会延长我们的生存时间
A source of water would stretch our survival.
你看到下雨的迹象了吗？
Did you see any evidence of rainfall?
不，长官，也没有证据表明以前下过雨
No, sir. I haven't seen any evidence that there ever has been rainfall.
但是有植被
But there is earth-type vegetation.
植被能从空气中吸收水分吗？
Is it possible the vegetation could absorb the water directly from the air?
是的，有可能，也可能有地下水
Yes, that's possible. There's also the possibility of underground water.
是的，长官，可能有
Yes, sir. Could be.
苏鲁探测到了一种类似病毒的生物
Sulu's picked up an organism that's almost a virus.
像一种植物寄生虫，这是我能找到的最接近生命的生物形式
Like a plant parasite. And it's the nearest biological form of life I can find.
这显然会是我们的家，只要我们活下去
This apparently is gonna our home for as long as we can last.
我建议我们尽可能多地了解它，分头行动
I suggest we find out as much as we can about it. Split out.
- 达马托，找找看是否有地下水  - 是的，长官
- D'Amato, see if you can find underground water. - Yes, sir.
- 苏鲁，进行大气分析  - 是的，长官
- Sulu, run an atmospheric analysis. - Aye, sir.
老骨头，看看你能不能找出关于植被和寄生虫的任何信息
Bones, see if you can find out anything about the vegetation and your parasite.
它们如何获得水分的？
How do they get their moisture?
如果你能发现它们是如何生存的，也许我们也可以
If you can discover how they survive, maybe we can.
苏鲁呼叫舰长
Sulu to Captain.
我是柯克
Kirk here.
我正在做一个标准的磁性扫描
Captain, I was making a standard magnetic sweep.
我得到了一个超出范围的读数
From zero I suddenly got a reading that was off the scale,
然后极性反转…现在又没了
then a reverse of polarity and... now I get nothing.
我从未见过这样的事情
I've not seen anything like this reading.
就像一扇门打开然后又关上
Like a door opened and then closed again.
通话完毕
Kirk out.
不要害怕
Do not be afraid.
我没有
I'm not.
地质扰动不会吓到我，我来这里就是研究它们
Geological disturbances don't frighten me. I come here to study them.
我的专长
My speciality.
我知道
I know.
你是达马托上尉，高级地质学家
You are Lieutenant D'Amato. Senior geologist.
没错，你怎么知道的？
That's right. How did you know that?
来自企业号
From the spaceship Enterprise.
是的，我们被困在这里
Yes, we're stranded here.
你和我的朋友说过话了吗？
Have you been talking to my friends?
不要害怕
Do not be afraid.
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
我是来找你的，达马托上尉
I am for you, Lieutenant D'Amato.
你是…你是企业号上的女人
You're...You're the woman on the Enterprise.
我只为了来找达马托
I am only for D'Amato.
幸运的达马托
Lucky D'Amato.
我想和你商量一下分享你的食物和水
Wanna have a conference about sharing your food and water.
不要叫其他人
Do not call the others.
拜托
Please.
麦考伊呼叫柯克
McCoy to Kirk.
我是柯克
Kirk here.
吉姆，我刚刚得到了一个巨大强度的生命形式读数
Jim, I just got a life-form reading of tremendous intensity.
突然间，它就在那里
Suddenly it was just there.
就在那里是什么意思？
What do you mean "just there"?
就是说
Just that.
所有水平都正常，然后显示生物激增
All levels were normal, then I get this biological surge of life-form registering.
不，现在没了
No. Now it's gone.
就像一扇门打开然后又关上
As though a door opened and closed.
是的
Yes.
什么方向？
What direction?
083.
等一下
Hang on.
达马托区，请回答
D'Amato's section, come in.
柯克呼叫达马托，请回答
Kirk to D'Amato. Come in.
请回答
Come in.
老骨头，苏鲁，达马托不回复
Bones, Sulu, D'Amato doesn't answer.
我马上过去
I'll be right there.
老骨头！
Bones!
他身体的每一个细胞都被破坏了
Jim, every cell in his body's been disrupted.
吉姆，你在做什么？
Jim, what are you doing?
挖坟
Digging a grave.
可怜的达马托，多么可怕的死亡方式
Poor D'Amato. What a terrible way to die.
没有好方式，苏鲁
There are no good ways, Sulu.
同样的红色岩石
That's the same red rock.
我的相位枪没能切开它
My phaser didn't cut through it.
它具有极高的熔点
Whatever it is, it has a mighty high melting point.
8,000摄氏度，它看起来像火成岩，但密度更大
8,000 degrees centigrade. It looks like igneous rock, but infinitely denser.
这整个星​​球一定由它组成，表层由土壤覆盖
This whole planet must be made up of this substance, covered over by top soil.
苏鲁先生，如果我们知道这物质是什么，也许能更好地解释这个地方
Mr. Sulu, it might explain this place a little better if we knew what the substance is.
我知道这本来是达马托负责的区域，但看看你能找到什么
I know it was D'Amato's field, but see what you can find out.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
我想石头墓是我们能为达马托提供的最好的东西
I guess a tomb of rocks is the best we can provide for D'Amato.
是的，这可能是最合适的纪念
Yeah. It might be the most suitable memorial at that.
我想知道是什么杀死了他
I wonder what killed him.
我不知道，但一定是什么东西或什么人干的
I don't know. But something or someone did.
我们正保持曲速8.4，长官
We're holding warp 8.4, sir.
如果我们保持这个速度，预计到达时间是11.5个太阳时
If we can maintain it, our estimated time of arrival is 11 and one half solar hours.
11.337小时，上尉，我希望你能更精确
11.337 hours, Lieutenant. I wish you would be more precise.
斯科特呼叫舰桥，斯科特呼叫舰桥
Scott to bridge. Scott to bridge.
- 我是史波克  - 史波克先生，这艘船感觉不对
- Spock here. - Mr. Spock, the ship feels wrong.
“感觉”，斯科特先生？
"Feels", Mr. Scott?
我知道这说不通，仪器读数正确，但感觉不对
I know it doesn't make sense. Instrumentation reads correct but the feel is wrong.
是我无法用语言表达的
It's something I can't put into words.
这很明显，斯科特先生
That is obvious, Mr. Scott.
避免情绪化并保持你的仪器正确
I suggest you avoid emotionalism and simply keep your instruments correct.
通话完毕
Spock out.
看起来很孤独
It looks so lonely there.
如果他有伴，那就更糟了
It would be worse if he had company.
医生，你怎么能拿它开玩笑呢？
Doctor, how can you joke about it?
我没有开玩笑，在我们知道是什么杀死了他之前，我们谁都不安全
I'm not joking. Until we know what killed him, none of us are safe.
我们必须弄明白并设计防御措施
We've got to figure this out and devise a defense against it.
有没有可能石头有生命？
Is it possible that the rocks have life?
- 你记得在杰纳斯六号上，硅基生物…  - 但我们的仪器记录了它
- You remember on Janus VI, the silicon creatures... - But our instruments recorded that.
他们显示为生命形式
They registered as life-forms.
除非我们与能够隐藏自己的智能生物打交道
Unless we're dealing with intelligent beings who can shield themselves.
智能到足以摧毁飞船？
Beings intelligent enough to destroy the Enterprise?
那就是问题所在，我们只有问题
That's the problem, Sulu. We have only questions.
没有答案
No answers.
沃特金斯
Watkins.
检查物质-反物质反应室上的旁通阀
Check the bypass valve on the matter-antimatter reaction chamber.
确保它没有过热
Make sure it's not overheating.
斯科特先生，面板显示正确
Mr. Scott, the board shows correct.
- 我没有让你检查面板  - 是的，长官
- I didn't ask you to check the board, lad. - Yes, sir.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我的名字并不重要，你叫沃特金斯，约翰B
My name is not important. Yours is Watkins, John B.
- 4级轮机员  - 你对我了如指掌
- Engineer Grade 4. - You know all about me.
我以前从未见过你
I've never seen you before.
给我展示这个装置，我想学习
Show me this unit. I wish to learn.
这是物质-反物质积分器控制
This is a matter-antimatter integrator control.
那是切断开关
That's the cutoff switch.
不对
Not correct.
那是紧急过载旁路，它瞬间就能启动
That is the emergency overload bypass, which engages almost instantaneously.
明智的预防措施，因为反物质需要更长的时间才能爆炸
A wise precaution considering it takes the antimatter longer to explode
一旦磁流失效
once the magnetic flow fails.
我是来找你的，沃特金斯先生
I am for you, Mr. Watkins.
斯科特先生，一个陌生的女人知道企业号的完整计划
Mr. Scott, a strange woman knows the entire plan of the Enterprise.
[尖叫]
[SCREAM]
哦，可怜的家伙
Oh, you poor lad.
斯科特呼叫舰桥，斯科特呼叫舰桥
Scott to bridge. Scott to bridge.
我是史波克
Spock here.
我的助手沃特金斯死了！
My assistant, Watkins, is dead!
你知道他为什么死吗，斯科特先生？
Do you know what he died of, Mr. Scott?
我没看到，但他最后的话是关于一个陌生女人的
I didn't see it, but his last words were about a strange woman.
安全警报，女性入侵者，极其危险
Security alert，all decks. Female intruder, extremely dangerous.
安全警报，所有甲板
Security alert, all decks.
结论
Conclusions.
这颗行星的物质是双燃锇合金
The basic substance of this planet is an alloy of diburnium-osmium.
它不可能是自然进化的
It couldn't have evolved naturally.
舰长，这说不通，事实上，这里的东西都说不通
Captain, it doesn't make sense. In fact, othing about this planet makes sense.
除了瞬间的波动，这颗行星没有磁场
Except for momentary fluctuations, this planet has no magnetic field.
这些岩石的表观年龄只有几千年
The apparent age of these rocks is only a few thousand years.
没有任何已知的过程可以在这么短的时间内进化出他们这里的植物生命
No known process could evolve the plant life they have here in that short space of time.
你是说这可能是一颗人造星球？
Are you suggesting this might be an artificial planet?
但是创造它的人在哪里？
But Captain where are the people who made it?
为什么我们看不到他们？
Why can't we see them?
这个星球可能是空心的
The planet may be hollow.
他们可能保护自己免受我们的传感器探头的影响
They might be shielding themselves from our sensor probes.
天黑了，我们休息一下吧
It's dark. Let's get some rest.
明天我们必须找到食物和水
Tomorrow we have to find food and water
否则将是一次很不愉快的逗留
or it's going to be a very unpleasant stay.
珍惜现在
While it lasts.
我来值第一班
I'll take the first watch.
好的，将达马托的三录仪设置为自动呼救
All right, set D'Amato's tricorder for automatic distress.
- 防患于未然  - 是的，长官
- You never can tell. - Aye, sir.
[哔哔]
[BLEEPING]
史波克呼叫医务室，你完成沃特金斯的尸检了吗，医生？
Spock to Sickbay. Have you completed the autopsy on Watkins, doctor?
[姆本加] 是的，完成了，史波克先生
[M'Benga] Yes, we have, Mr. Spock.
他的死因和传送人员一样吗？
Was the cause of his death the same as that which killed the transporter officer?
细胞破裂的模式是相同的
The pattern of of cellular disruption was the same.
但至于原因，你的猜测和我的一样
But as to the cause, your guess is as good as mine.
医生，我的猜测毫无价值
My guess, Doctor, would be valueless.
不要猜测，找出一些事实，通话完毕
I suggest we refrain from guessing and find some facts. Spock out.
入侵者破坏身体每一个细胞的力量
The power of this intruder to disrupt every cell in a body,
加上将企业号扔出这么远的距离所需的力量
combined with the power required to hurl the Enterprise such a distance,
都说明了一种非常高的文化和非常大的危险
speak of a very high culture and a very great danger.
你是说把我们扔到1000光年外的人
You mean that one of the people that threw us 1,000 light years away from that planet
在船上并且在杀人？
is on board and killing our people?
一个合理的假设，斯科特先生
A reasonable assumption, Mr. Scott.
那么你是对的，史波克先生，沃特金斯一定是被谋杀了
Then you're right, Mr. Spock. Watkins must have been murdered.
我派他去检查物质-反物质反应堆
I sent him in to check the matter-antimatter reactor.
那里没有暴露的电路
There are no exposed circuits there.
不可能是他碰过的东西
It couldn't have been anything he touched.
如果那个星球上有更多这样的生物
If there are more of those beings on that planet,
舰长和其他人处于非常危险的境地
the captain and the others are in very great danger.
我没有武器
I am unarmed.
你是谁？
Who are you?
那不重要
That is not important.
你是苏鲁上尉
You are Lieutenant Sulu.
你出生在地球上
You were born on the planet Earth.
你是企业号的舵手
You are helmsman for the Enterprise.
你怎么知道？你从哪儿弄的信息？
How do you know? Where did you get this information?
你来自这个星球吗？
Are you from this planet?
我来自这里
I am from here.
那么行星确实是空心的
Then the planet is hollow.
谁杀死了达马托上尉？
Who killed Lieutenant D'Amato?
舰长会想和你谈谈的，那边
All right, the captain wanna talk to you. That way.
走
Move.
你不明白，我是来找你的
You do not understand. I have come for you.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我想…碰你
I want... to touch you.
你之前在企业号上
You were on the Enterprise.
靠后！停下，否则我就开枪！
Keep back! Stop or I'll shoot!
我不想杀女人
I don't want to have to kill a woman.
柯克舰长！柯克舰长！
Captain Kirk! Captain Kirk!
[苏鲁大喊]
[SULU SHOUTS]
别动
Hold it.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我来找他，我来找苏鲁上尉
I am for him. I am for Lieutenant Sulu.
不要让她碰你，舰长！
Don't let her touch you, Captain!
达马托就是这样死的
That's how D'Amato died.
相位枪不能阻止她
Phasers won't stop her.
我来找苏鲁上尉，拜托，我必须碰他
I am for Lieutenant Sulu. Please. I must touch him.
为什么你能毁灭别人但不是我？
How can you destroy others and not me?
我不想毁灭，我不想
I don't want to destroy. I don't want to.
你是谁？你为什么要杀我们？
Who are you? Why are you trying to kill us?
只要苏鲁
Only Sulu.
我不会伤害你的
I mean you no harm.
这个星球上有人吗？
Are there men on this planet?
拜托，我一定要碰他，我来找苏鲁上尉
Please, I must touch him. I am for Lieutenant Sulu.
不！
No!
老骨头，你看到了吗？
Bones, did you see that?
也许史波克错了，或许这是一个幽灵星球
Maybe Spock was wrong. Perhaps this is a ghost planet.
我只知道她差点把苏鲁变成鬼魂
All I know is she almost made a ghost out of Sulu.
他肩膀上，她碰过的地方，每个细胞都从内部炸开了
His shoulder, where she touched it, every cell's been disrupted, exploded from within.
如果她紧紧地抓住了他…
If she'd gotten a good grip on him, Jim...
人怎么能，舰长？
How can such people be, Captain?
如此邪恶，她真…真漂亮
Such evil, and she's so... so beautiful.
是的，我知道
Yes, I know.
所有甲板的安全扫描都没有情况，史波克先生，没有入侵者的证据
Security sweeps of all decks are negative, Mr. Spock. No evidence of intruder.
很好，取消红色警报但维持更强的安全措施
Very well. Cancel Red Alert but maintain increased security.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
所有甲板取消红色警报，维持更强的安全措施
All decks, cancel Red Alert. Maintain increased security.
更新我们对星际舰队的报告以包括安全搜索，结果没有情况
Update our report to Starfleet to include security search, results negative.
她是怎么下船的，长官？
How did she get off the ship, sir?
大概和她上船的方式一样
Presumably the same way she got on.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
史波克先生，舰长和其他人还活着的几率有多大？
Mr. Spock, what are the chances of the captain and the others being alive?
上尉，我们不参与赌博
Lieutenant, we are not engaged in gambling.
我们正在以合乎逻辑的方式继续
We are proceeding in the logical way
回到最后一次见到他们的地方，并实际确定
to return to the place they were last seen and factually ascertain
他们是否还活着
whether or not they still live.
是的，史波克先生
Yes, Mr. Spock.
史波克先生，速度提高到了曲速8.8
Mr. Spock, speed has increased to warp 8.8.
轮机部呼叫舰桥
Bridge to engineering.
我是斯科提，我看到了
Scotty here. I see it.
能量激增，我正在努力
It's a power surge. I'm working on it.
减速，直到我找到问题所在
Reduce speed till I locate the trouble.
很好，减速至曲速7
Very well. Reduce speed to warp 7.
是的，长官，曲速7
Aye, sir. Warp 7.
史波克先生，我们的速度已增加到曲速8.9并且仍在攀升
Mr. Spock. Our speed has increased to warp 8.9 and still climbing.
舰桥呼叫轮机部
Bridge to engineering.
无法减速
Negative effect on power reduction.
速度还在增加
Speed is still increasing.
是的，史波克先生，我已经找到原因了
Aye, Mr. Spock, and I've found out why.
物质-反物质积分器的紧急旁路控制已熔断
The emergency bypass control of the matter-antimatter integrator is fused.
完全没用了
It's completely useless.
引擎疯狂运转，没有办法对付他们
The engines are running wild. There's no way to get at them.
我们将在15分钟内达到最大过载
Except reach maximum overload in 15 minutes.
我会算14.87分钟，斯科特先生
I would calculate 14.87 minutes, Mr. Scott.
那几秒钟不会有任何区别
Those few seconds will not make any difference,
因为你我和其余船员将不再在这里来回穿梭
because you and I and the rest of the crew will no longer be here to bandy it back and forth.
这东西要爆炸了
This thing is going to blow up.
宇宙中没有任何东西可以阻止它
And there's nothing in the universe can stop it.
有一层几个细胞厚的坏死组织
There's a layer of necrotic tissue a few cells thick.
正常的伤口会很快愈合
A normal wound would heal quickly.
她只是…碰了我
She just... touched me.
怎么会这么快？
How could it happen so fast?
这是个好问题
That's a good question.
她触到了传送长官，他立刻倒下了
She touched the transporter chief and he collapsed immediately.
她显然碰到了达马托
She apparently got to D'Amato.
我们看到了他的遭遇
We saw what happened to him.
问题是，你为什么活着？
The question is, why are you alive?
舰长，我很高兴是这个结果
Captain, I'm happy the way it turned out.
吉姆
Jim.
她必须拥有什么样的力量？
What kind of power must she have?
完全破坏生物细胞结构的能力
The power to totally disrupt biological cell structure.
苏鲁还活着是因为我介入了
Sulu's alive because I intervened.
但这提出了一个更糟糕的问题
But that raises an even worse question.
是的
Yes.
她为什么不杀你？
Why didn't she kill you?
她还没有完成
She's not through yet.
没用的，毫无疑问，这是故意的
It's useless. And there is no question, it's deliberate.
蓄意破坏
Sabotage.
是的，缜密的工作
Aye. And a thorough job.
系统不会出错
The system's foolproof.
谋杀沃特金斯的人破坏了它
Whoever murdered Watkins sabotaged it.
你说它被熔断了，怎么做的？
You said it was fused. How?
那就是困扰我的事
That's what worries me.
“困扰”，斯科特先生？
"Worries," Mr. Scott?
嗯，它是熔断了
Well, it's fused,
但做到这一点需要我们相位炮台的所有能量
but it would take all the power of our phaser banks to do it.
有趣
Interesting.
我不觉得我们即将爆炸的事实有趣
I find nothing interesting in the fact we're about to blow up.
不，但是方法很吸引人
No. But the method is fascinating.
干了这事的东西仍然在这艘船上
Whatever did this is still aboard this ship.
我不理解你为什么取消安全警报
I fail to understand why you cancelled the security alert.
一种可以将我们抛向990.7光年之外的力量
A force that could hurl us 990.7 light years away
并且仍然能够破坏我们的主要能源
and at that distance still be able to sabotage our main source of energy
不会坐以待毙
will not be waiting around to be taken into custody.
也是
Aye.
当我回忆起我们燃料流的模式时
As I recall the pattern of our fuel flow,
有一根通向物质-反物质反应室的管道
there is an access tube leading to the matter-antimatter reaction chamber.
有一条爬行通道
There's a service crawlway,
但它不适合在积分器运行时使用
but it's not meant to be used while the integrator operates.
然而，它还在
Still, it is there.
也许可以在那里切断燃料的流动
And it might be possible to shut off the flow of fuel at that point.
用什么？空手？
What with? Bare hands?
一个磁性探头
A magnetic probe.
任何与反物质接触的物质都会引发爆炸
Any matter that comes in contact with antimatter triggers the explosion.
我不确定人能不能在爬行通道里活下来
And I'm not even sure a man can live in a crawlway
在装着反物质的磁场的能量流中
in the energy stream of the magnetic field that bottles up the antimatter.
我会试试的
I shall try.
你会被杀的，兄弟
You'll be killed, man.
除非迅速找到解决办法
Unless a solution is found quickly,
否则我们所有人都会死
that fate awaits all of us.
是的，你说得对，我们有什么能失去的呢？
Aye. You're right. What have we got to lose?
但我来做吧，史波克先生
But I'll do it, Mr. Spock.
我对那个系统了如指掌
I know every millimeter of that system.
我会做该做的事
I'll do whatever has to be done.
很好，斯科特先生
Very well, Mr. Scott.
你谈到了船出错的感觉
You spoke of the feel of the ship being wrong.
是的，这是一个情绪化的陈述，我不指望你能理解
Aye. It was an emotional statement. I don't expect you to understand it.
斯科特先生，我注意到了这一点，但不一定理解它
I note it, Mr. Scott, without necessarily understanding it.
我会用计算机进行分析
I propose to run an analysis through the ship's computers,
比较企业号的现状与她的理想状态
comparing the present condition of the Enterprise with her ideal condition.
我们没有时间这样做
Mr. Spock, we don't have time for that.
我们有12分27秒
We have 12 minutes and 27 seconds.
在我学习计算机的同时，在爬行通道里尽你所能
I suggest you do whatever you can in the service crawlway while I make the computer study.
你觉得足够强壮可以走动吗？
Lieutenant Sulu, do you feel strong enough to move on?
我感觉很好，舰长
I feel fine, Captain.
是吗，老骨头？
Is he, Bones?
他的状态还不错
He's in fair shape.
好的
All right.
无论这个女人有多大破坏力她似乎每次只针对一个人
Whatever destructive power this woman has seems to be aimed at one specific person at one specific time.
如果我没猜错，当她再次出现时
If I'm correct, when she reappears,
另外两个也许能保护她追捕的人
the other two might be able to protect the one she's after
挡在他们之间
by interposing their bodies.
似乎没有武器能伤到她
No weapons seem to affect her.
她怎么认识我们的？
Captain, how does she know about us?
她会读心术吗？
Does she read our minds?
相位枪过载！
Phaser on overload!
控制器熔断了，扔掉！
Controls are fused. Droped!
显然，她可以摧毁我们的武器
Apparently she can destroy our weapons
就像摧毁我们一样
as well as destroy us.
快点，我们走
Come on. Let's go.
好的，小伙子们，打开爬行通道门
All right, lads. Get the crawlway door open.
把工具递给我
Hand me the tools.
通讯器，好的，头先进
Communicator. All right. Head first.
我希望史波克先生知道他在做什么
I hope Mr. Spock knows what he's doing.
斯科特呼叫舰桥
Scott to bridge.
[史波克] 请讲，斯科特先生
[Spock] Go ahead, Mr. Scott.
我已经封锁了爬行通道的尾端
I've sealed off the aft end of the crawlway
并放置了爆炸分离炸药
and positioned explosive separator charges
如果我打破了磁性瓶，就把我轰出飞船
to blast me clear of the ship if I rupture the magnetic bottle.
我现在非常接近磁流，感觉就像蚂蚁在我的全身爬行
I'm so close to the flow now it feels like ants crawling all over my body.
斯科特先生，我建议你避免更多的主观描述
Mr. Scott, I suggest you refrain from any further subjective descriptions.
你有10分19秒的时间来执行你的任务
You now have 10 minutes and 19 seconds in which to perform your task.
[拉达] 史波克先生，我们在曲速11.2并且不断加速
[Radha] Mr. Spock. We're at warp 11.2 and accelerating.
我听到了，这艘船的结构不能承受这种速度
I heard that. The ship's not structured to take that speed for any length of time.
你现在有10分10秒
You now have 10 minutes and 10 seconds.
好的，史波克先生，我正开始打开检修板
All right, Mr. Spock. I'm starting to open the access panel now.
磁流的入口
Access to the flow itself.
如果磁流跳跃，你必须抛弃我
If the magnetic flow jumps, you must jettison me.
安全控制不会坚持超过两秒
The safety control will not hold more than two seconds
如果我破坏了场
if I rupture the field.
我知道这些事实，请继续工作
I'm aware of these facts. Please get on with the job.
计算机
Computer.
工作中
Working.
分析我的对比坐标
Analysis on my comparison coordinates.
[计算机] 无法运行
[Computer] Unable to comply.
对比坐标太复杂，无法立即读出
Comparison coordinates too complex for immediate read-out.
将在完成后通知
Will advise upon completion.
我已卸下检修板
I've removed the access plate
我看到电荷在仪器上跳跃
and I've got static electric charges dancing on the instruments.
看起来那里面像有极光
Looks like an aurora borealis in there.
乌乎拉上尉，你在监测磁力？
Lieutenant Uhura, you are monitoring the magnetic force?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
一定不要开小差
Please do not take your eyes off it.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
拉达上尉，装备分离仓抛弃系统
Lieutenant Radha, arm the pod jettison system.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
有问题我会立即抛弃
I'll jettison at the first sign of trouble.
我下令再执行
Not until my order.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
曲速11.9
Warp 11.9.
斯科特先生，你的情况如何？
Mr. Scott, what is your situation?
很难说
It's hard to see.
有太多的干扰，任何接近磁流的尝试
There's so much disturbance that any attempt to get at the flow
都会破坏磁场
would rupture the magnetic field.
你有8分41秒
You have 8 minutes, 41 seconds.
我知道时间，我不需要报时的布谷鸟钟
I know what time it is. I don't need a bloomin' cuckoo clock.
舰长，我又遇到了那种奇怪的磁性扫描，从0到超出范围
Captain, I'm getting that strange magnetic sweep again, from zero to off the scale.
是的
Yes.
就像一扇门…打开…
Like a door... opening...
你这次来找谁？
Who have you come for this time?
找你，詹姆斯·T·柯克
For you, James T. Kirk.
企业号的指挥官
Commander of the Enterprise.
躲在我们身后，吉姆
Keep behind us, Jim.
你为什么要杀我们？
Why do you wanna kill us?
为了防御
For defense.
你是詹姆斯·T·柯克舰长，企业号的指挥官
You are Captain James T. Kirk, commander of the Enterprise.
那么你为什么要杀我？
Then why do you wanna kill me?
你是入侵者
You are an invader.
我们在这执行和平任务，是你杀了我们的人
We're here on a peaceful mission. It's you who have killed our people.
我们无意伤害，我们想平静地离开
We mean no harm to you. We want to leave peacefully.
舰长，没有生命形式显示
Captain, I'm getting no life-form register.
机器人？
An android?
那会给出机械读数，我什么都没读到
That would give a mechanical reading. I'm getting nothing.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是洛西拉，指挥官
I am Losira, Commander.
什么的指挥官？
Commander of what?
这个站
Of this station.
站？哪里有站？
Station? Station, where?
杀死我的感觉怎么样？
How do you feel about killing me?
感觉？
Feel?
杀戮…是错误的
Killing... is wrong.
躲在我们中间！
Stay between us!
你不能进入这个站！
You must not penetrate this station!
拜托，我必须碰你！
Please, I must touch you!
你要杀我？
You want to kill me?
不
No.
那为什么要这样做，如果你不想？
Then why do it, if you don't want to?
我…被派来
I am... sent.
被谁？
By whom?
我们保卫这个地方
We defend this place.
这个星球上还有其他人吗？
Are there others on this planet?
他们…已经…不在了
They... are... no more.
你一个人多久了？
How long have you been alone?
你孤独吗？
Are you lonely?
她一定在某个地方
She must be somewhere.
她没有显示
She's not registering.
还有这种能量激增，完全超出范围
And there's this power surge, right off the scale.
就像关门一样
Like a door closing.
应该就在这附近
It must be near here.
能量水平仍然不变？
Is the power level still holding?
超出范围
Right off the scale.
自从她消失以来，它一直处于峰值
It's remained at a peak since she disappeared.
入口在这里
The entrance is here.
你认为我们是被邀请进来的？
You think we're being invited in?
无疑看起来像，
It certainly looks like it.
邀请并没有让我完全放松
And the invitation doesn't exactly relax me.
我宁愿在企业号上
I'd rather be on the Enterprise.
我同意
I agree.
我们被带到这里，为什么？
We've been led here. Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是无论这个星球上存在什么文明都在那里面
But whatever civilization exists on this planet is in there.
而且没有企业号，先生们，食物和水的唯一来源
And without the Enterprise, gentlemen, the only source of food and water
也在那里面
is in there.
我们走
Let's go.
电脑读出
Computer read-out.
[计算机] 对比分析完成
[Computer] Comparison analysis complete.
继续
Continue.
传送系数M7重组反相.0009
Transporter factor M7 reassembled out-phase .0009.
还剩57秒，长官
57 seconds to go, sir.
了解
Understood.
史波克先生 -
Mr. Spock
我是史波克
Spock here.
我要试着切断磁流
I'm going to try to cut through the magnetic flow.
但如果探头不能精确匹配磁流
But if the probe doesn't precisely match the magnetic flow,
会爆炸
there will be an explosion.
现在…开始
Starting right... now.
磁力指示器跳跃
Magnetic force indicator jumping, Mr. Spock.
斯科特先生，放轻松
Mr. Scott, ease off.
磁力已降至正常
Magnetic force has dropped to normal, sir.
曲速13.2，长官
Warp 13.2, sir.
计算机，在反相情况下，逆转磁场会实现闭合吗？
Computer, for out-phase condition, will reverse field achieve closure?
[电脑] 是的，如果M7系数保持不变
[Computer] Affirmative, if M7 factor maintained.
斯科特先生，翻转你的磁性探头极性
Mr. Scott, reverse polarity on your magnetic probe.
翻转极性？
Reverse polarity?
没错，斯科特先生
That is correct, Mr. Scott.
这需要做一些工作，它有什么目的…
That will take some doing. What purpose could it...
请开始，我会解释
Please commence. I'll explain.
你的“感觉”是正确的
You were correct in your "feel".
我们经历了一次传送
The Enterprise was put through a molecular transporter
然后被反相重组了
and reassembled slightly out of phase.
翻转极性应该会封上切口
Reverse polarity should seal the incision.
我只希望你是对的
No time for theory, just hope you're right.
[拉达] 20秒，史波克先生
[Radha] 20 seconds, Mr. Spock.
我正在尽我所能
I'm doing the best I can.
等等！
Wait!
卡住了！
It's stuck!
卡住了！按按钮！
It's stuck! Push the button!
请继续
Please continue.
别傻了！按按钮！
Don't be a fool! Push the button!
这是你最后的机会！
It's your last chance!
不要感情用事，按按钮
Don't be sentimental. Push it!
反正我会死
I'm gonna die anyway.
请继续
Please continue.
松开了！但是没时间了，按按钮！
It's loose! But there's no time. Push the button!
9秒…8秒…7秒…
9 seconds... 8 seconds... 7 seconds...
6秒…5秒…4秒…
6 seconds... 5 seconds... 4 seconds...
3秒…2秒…1…
3 seconds... 2 seconds... 1...
史波克先生，现在
Mr. Spock, now.
曲速14.1…
Warp 14.1...
曲速14
Warp 14.
磁力稳定
Magnetic forces steady.
曲速13.9并且在下降
Warp 13.9 and dropping.
斯科特先生，你已经完成了你的任务
Mr. Scott, you have accomplished your task.
你至少可以说声谢谢
You might at least say thank you.
为什么，斯科特先生？在你们人类身上…
For what purpose, Mr. Scott? What is it in you humans...
算了
Never mind.
有什么东西需要在这样的情况下表现出压倒性的情绪呢？
That requires an overwhelming display of emotion in a situation such as this?
两个人采取唯一合理的行动方案
Two men pursue the only reasonable course of action indicated
然而你觉得其他的东西是必要的
and yet you feel that something else is necessary.
你来找谁？
Who have you come for?
围成圆圈
Form a circle.
你看？你最好告诉我们
You see? You'd better tell us.
告诉我们，你来找谁？
Tell us. Who have you come for?
你来找谁？
Who have you come for?
你是一位很坚决的女性，找我？
You're a very determined woman. For me?
我找詹姆斯T.柯克
I am for James T. Kirk.
先生们，我需要你们的帮助
Gentlemen, I need your help.
拜托
Please.
我必须碰你，我求你了，这是我的生存方式
I must touch you. I beg it. It is my existence.
我们已经看到了你触摸的后果
We've seen the results of your touch.
但你是我匹配的人，詹姆斯·柯克，我必须碰你
But you are my match, James Kirk. I must touch you.
然后我会像你一样活着，甚至复刻你的细胞结构
Then I will live as one, even to the structure of your cells,
染色体的排列
the arrangement of chromosomes.
这就是你杀人的方式
That is how you kill.
你永远都碰不到我
You'll never reach me.
小心！
Watch out!
我找麦考伊
I am for McCoy.
那台计算机一定在编写这些复制品
That computer must be programming these replicas.
她们碰到我们后与我们的染色体模式相匹配
The women match our chromosome patterns after they touch us.
我告诉你，那是一件很痛苦的事
It's a very painful affair. I can tell you.
我找苏鲁
I am for Sulu.
换位置
Shift positions.
我们不能再互相保护了
Captain, we can no longer protect each other.
史波克！电脑！破坏它！
Spock! The computer! Destroy it!
史波克先生，很高兴见到你
Mr. Spock, I certainly am glad to see you.
我以为你和企业号已经被摧毁了
I thought you and the Enterprise had been destroyed.
我对你也有同样的担忧
I had the same misgivings about you, Captain.
我们刚刚返回并读取了你的生命形式读数
We returned and picked up your life-form readings only a moment ago.
从哪里返回？
Returned from where?
从大脑把企业号送去的地方：
From where this brain had the power to send the Enterprise:
横跨银河系990.7光年
990.7 light years across the galaxy.
这是多么了不起的文化
What a remarkable culture this is.
曾是，史波克先生，它的防御是由计算机运行的
Was, Mr. Spock. Its defenses were run by computer.
我猜到了，舰长
I surmised that, Captain.
它的行为非常合乎逻辑
Its moves were immensely logical.
但是什么人创造了这个？
But what people created this?
这里有代表吗？
Are there any representatives here?
有其中一个的复制品
There were replicas of one of them.
但是创造他们的能量已经被摧毁了
But the power to recreate them has been destroyed.
真是个损失，舰长
That is a loss, Captain.
如果你和我们一起，你就不会这么想了
You wouldn't have thought so if you'd been among us.
我的卡兰丹同伴，欢迎
My fellow Kalandans, welcome.
一种疾病摧毁了我们，当心它
A disease has destroyed us. Beware of it.
在你长途跋涉之后，很抱歉只给你一个录音欢迎
After your long journey, I'm sorry to give you only a recorded welcome.
但我们守卫前哨站的人
But we who have guarded the outpost for you
已经死了，到你占领星球时
will be dead by the time you take positions on this planet.
我是我们先进部队中最后一个还活着的人
I am the last of our advanced force left alive.
医生发现我们生病的原因时已经太晚了
Too late, the physicians discovered the cause of our sickness.
在创造这个星球的过程中
In creating this planet,
我们意外地产生了一种致命的生物
we have accidentally produced a deadly organism.
我一直在等待来自家乡的补给船寻求医疗援助
I have awaited the regular supply ship from home for medical assistance,
但我现在怀疑它是否会及时到达
but I doubt now whether it will arrive in time.
我会将前哨站控制设置为自动
I will set the outpost controls on automatic.
计算机将抵御除我们自己以外的所有生命形式
The computer will defend against all life-forms but our own.
我的卡兰丹同伴
My fellow Kalandans,
我，洛西拉，祝你一切顺利
I, Losira, wish you well.
先前的船只可能通过他们的人民传播这种疾病
The previous ships probably spread the disease all through their people.
她等的补给船一直没有来
The supply ship she waited for never came.
几千年来，她一直在等待迎接死去的人
All these thousands of years she's been waiting to greet people who were dead.
为了防卫工作
To do the job of defense,
计算机投影了唯一可用图像的复制品
the computer projected a replica of the only image available
洛西拉的
Losira's.
电脑太完美了
The computer was too perfect.
它把洛西拉的个性投射到复制品中
It projected so much of Losira's personality into the replica
它对杀戮感到后悔，内疚
that it felt regret, guilt, at killing.
这为我们赢得了摧毁它所需的时间
That bought us the time we needed to destroy it.
她一定是…一个了不起的女人
She must have been... a remarkable woman.
而且很漂亮
And beautiful.
美丽是短暂的，医生
Beauty is transitory, Doctor.
然而，她显然是非常聪明的
However, she was, evidently, highly intelligent.
柯克呼叫企业号，传送五个人上船
Kirk to Enterprise. Five to beam up.
我不同意你的看法，史波克先生
I don't agree with you, Mr. Spock.
真的吗，舰长？
Indeed, captain?
美…会留存下来
Beauty... survives.